Griffin Quarles, Front-end Web Developer

Evansville, IN, 812-480-8391, griffinquarles11@gmail.com

LINKS	$griffin quarles. net lify. app, \\ https://www.linkedin.com/in/griffin squarles/, \\ https://github.com/gsquarles/, \\ https://github$	
PROFILE	I'm a web developer with proficiency in a variety of front-end technologies. I like building user-centered digits experiences that are both visually appealing and highly functional. Excited to leverage my skills and constantly learn and grow as a developer.	
PROJECTS	Where's Wally	
	Created full stack Where's Wally game using Firebase, React, and Tailwind	
	 CSS Find the characters on the map and record your time to see if you made the leader boards. <u>Github</u> 	
	Shopping Cart	
	Designed and developed a mock eCommerce Site with React and Tailwind	
	 Css. Allows you to add items to cart and adjust number of items keeping live track of prices in cart. <u>Github</u> 	
	Memory Game	
	 Memory Game built with React and Tailwind CSS. As the name suggests it is a game to test users' memory. The cards shuffle after every selection. The goal is to maximize your score by not selecting the same card again. <u>Github</u> 	
	Business Website	
	 Small business site built using React, Tailwind CSS, and Formspree. A website built for a small business a friend and I created. <u>Github</u> 	
EDUCATION		
Jun 2021 — Present	Full Stack Javascript, The Odin Project	
	 Successfully completed Front-End Web Development course. Followed software engineering best practices and completed the assigned projects. 	
Aug 2016 — Dec 2020	Bachelors of Science Elementary Education, University of Southern Indiana	Evansville, IN
	 Graduated with magna cum laude honors 3 years of College baseball	
SKILLS	 Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS Libraries & Frameworks: React, Tailwind, Jest, Vitest Tools & Platforms: Firebase, Webpack, Git, Github, Netlify 	
WORK EXPERIENCE		
Ian 2021 — Present	6th Grade Math Teacher	Evansville, IN

Jan 2021 — Present

6th Grade Math Teacher

Evansville, IN

- Developed engaging lesson plans utilizing hands-on activities and technology, resulting in a 80% of students meeting their end of the year growth goal.
- Collaborated with co-teacher to create a comprehensive review guide for end-of-year testing, resulting in an increase from 3 to 33 students passing end-of-year state test.